



Try Premium Free for 1 Month



Connect

**♠** Message

• • •

Hau Ly · 3rd

Manager at 500 Startups Vietnam | we are investing and hiring!

Vietnam · 500+ connections · Contact info



500 Startups Vietnam



Hanoi University

## Highlights

### Reach out to Hau for...

Probono consulting and volunteering, Joining a nonprofit board.

Message

#### About

Manager at 500 Startups Vietnam. Previously, I worked across marketing and operations functions at an entrepreneurship center, microfinance institution, and several startups in the U.S., Germany, and Vietnam. At 500 Startups Vietnam, I am focused on investment and fund operations.

## Activity

769 followers



hay quá chị ơi!

Hau commented



Join us in supporting the next best startups in Vietnam! #wearehirin...

Hau shared this 9 Reactions

See all activity

## Experience

#### **500 Startups Vietnam**



yrs 9 mos

## Manager

an 2018 – Present

· 3 yrs 4 mos

Vietnam

500 Startups Vietnam is a \$14 million fund to invest in 80-100 Vietnam-connected startups by 2020. We provide finance, mentorship, and connections to both global and regional startups. Our phở -nomenal portfolio companies are pioneering fintech, ecommerce, logistics, adtech, edtech, and other verticals.

https://vietnam.500.co/

#### **Associate**

Feb 2017 - Jan 2018

1 yr

Vietnam

#### **Assistant & Analyst**

Aug 2016 - Feb 2017

· 7 mos

Vietnam

#### Microfinance Officer

The Dariu Foundation



DARIU FOUR DATION · less than a year

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

The Dariu Foundation is a Swiss foundation operating in Vietnam, Myanmar & India, with the mission to empower low-income families via microfinance and education projects.

- Supervised microfinance activities in the Mekong region via regular site visits & internal audits
- Assisted the Director on expansions to Myanmar & India

#### Intern

Various organizations

2012 - 2015

· 3 yrs

U.S., Germany, Vietnam

Organizations included Operation Smile Vietnam (international medical charity - Vietnam), bab.la GmbH (startup - Germany), ClickableMass (coworking space - Vietnam), and Grand Valley State University (GVSU)'s Center of Entrepreneurship & Innovation (CEI) (entrepreneurship support - U.S.)

- Established and launched bab.la's Vietnamese website
- Assisted CEI in conducting GVSU 5th Annual Business Plan Competition, Ernst & Young Entrepreneur of the Year Award, and the Annual Family Business Survey. see more

## Education

### **Hanoi University**

Bachelor's degree, English Studies and Finance & Banking (double major)

Activities and Societies: U.S. Embassy's Vietnam Social Entrepreneurship Empowerment & Development project (Founding Member) and Students in Free Enterprise (SIFE) Hanoi University (President)

- Scholarship recipient, U.S. Department of State's Global Undergraduate Exchange Program (2011-2012)
- Finalist, AmCham Scholars Program by the American Chamber of Commerce Hanoi (2012)

### **Grand Valley State University**

2011 – 2012

Global Undergraduate (Global UGRAD) Exchange Program, Finance & Banking

Exchange student, U.S. Department of State's Global Undergraduate Exchange Program (2011-2012)

## **Hanoi Amsterdam High School for the Gifted**

English, Chinese Mandarin 2005 - 2008

## Accomplishments



### Languages

English • Vietnamese

## Interests

#### Leflair

3,370 followers



#### VinaHR - Top HR Network in Vietnam



36,060 members

#### VinaHR - Marketing Jobs in Vietnam



### Ray Dalio in



Co-Chief Investment Officer & Co-Chairman of Bridgewater Associates, L.P.

,060,516 followers

#### **Headhunt Vietnam**



NetViet 3,958 members

### **Grand Valley State University**



112,698 followers

# People also viewed



□ **Dzung Dang •**3rd We are hiring!

Connect



Binh Tran •3rd in

General Partner at 500 Startups Vietnam

Connect



**Huyen My Duong •**3rd **Toperations Coordinator** 

Connect



Kim Duong •3rd

Product Executive at Nano Technologies Pte Ltd

Connect



**alan nguyen •**3rd

EIR at 500 Startups Vietnam

Connect

**Show more Show more** 

# People you may know



BE BA (My Nguyen)

Recruitment Specialist cum Admin at Milensea Retail

Connect



Le Nhat Huy

President at UTE Logistics and Supply Chain Club

Connect



Khánh Linh Đỗ

Human Resources Assistant at Hachinet Software

Connect



Nguyen Dinh Dat

Frontend Angular Developer

Connect



Nhi Duong

Connect			
→ Show more			
in LEARNING			
Add new skills with these courses			
All n Fintech Essential Training			
25,771 viewers			
A Manager's Toolkit for Supporting Change			
13,040 viewers			
Brad Feld on Raising Capital			
209,301 viewers			
Show more on LinkedIn Learning			
Linked in			
About			
Accessibility			
Talent Solutions			
Community Guidelines			

Student at Ton Duc Thang University

	r/.
LinkedIn Corporation © 2021	
(Arabic) العربية	
Select Language	
Go to your Settings.	
Manage your account and privacy	
visit our Help Center.	
Questions?	
Safety Center	
Small Business	
Mobile Control of the	
Sales Solutions	
Advertising	
Ad Choices	
Privacy & Terms ❤	
Marketing Solutions	
Careers Careers	

